（デイダラ）フッ
（我愛羅があら）ん？
（デイダラ）う…
（砂すなの里さとの忍しのび）うわあ…
（砂の里の忍）あ… なんだ？
Wh-What's that?
Just a little more.
（デイダラ）もう少しだ
あっ
You're pretty good.
なかなかやるなあ うん
（デイダラ）ほう 便利な人柱力(じんちゅうりき)だな
Now that's a handy Jinchuriki.
（デイダラ）しかし
オイラが よく分かったな
But...how'd you know
I was the intruder?
この砂漠に そんな鳥はいない
There are no birds like that
in this desert.
なるほど
I see.
♪～
～♪
The Jinchuriki of the Sand
なかなかやるなあ うん
You're pretty good...
Now that's a handy Jinchuriki.
（デイダラ）ほう 便利な人柱力だな
（デイダラ）しかし
オイラが よく分かったな
But...how'd you know
I was the intruder?
There are no birds like that
in this desert.
この砂漠に そんな鳥はいない
I see.
なるほど
Hey! What was that noise earlier?!
（砂の里の忍）おい
さっきの物音はなんだ
You're supposed to report immediately
if something happens...
何かあったら すぐ報告を…
あ…
こ これは…
Wh-What...happened?
ああっ
Lord Kazekage...
風影かぜかげ様
What do you mean something strange
got into the village?!
（カンクロウ）変なのが
里に入り込んでいるって
どういうことだ
里の守りは 由良ゆうら隊長が
がっちり固めてるはずじゃん
Captain Yura was supposed to have
tightened village security.
Actually... we have been unable to
contact Captain Yura.
（砂の里の忍）それが…
その由良隊長と
連絡がつかない状態なのです
Come again?!
なんだと？
Oh, man...That Deidara had to go
and turn this into a circus.
（サソリ）あ～あ
結局 大騒ぎにしちまって
デイダラのやつ
由良
Yura.
You head on back.
お前 先に行ってろ
里の連中に見つかると
いろいろと面倒だからな
Things will get complicated if the guys
from the village find you here.
Yes, Lord Sasori.
（由良）はっ サソリ様
Get a move on, Deidara.
（サソリ）早くしろよ デイダラ
I don't like to be kept waiting.
俺は 待たされるのが
好きじゃねえからな
（カンクロウ）我愛羅 入るぞ
Gaara! I'm coming in!
Where'd he go...?
どこに行ったんだ
（砂の里の忍）カンクロウ
Kankuro, the Kazekage is fighting
up in the sky.
風影様が 上で戦ってらっしゃるぞ
Wh-What did you say?
なっ なんだと！
我愛羅
Gaara...!
ハッ
隠密行動は失敗だな うん
The covert action is a failure.
ハハッ
だが おかげで
てめえを捜す手間が省けたぜ
But now...
I don't have to bother...
looking for you anymore...!
（我愛羅）んんっ！
ああ…
さすが地の利があるか
He's got the advantage,
as expected...
やっかいだな うん
This is a real mess.
Over there?!
（ナルト）そこか！
（カカシ）あっ
（カカシ）こいつは…
This one is?!
A transformation of one
of Naruto's Shadow Clones, huh?!
ナルトの影分身かげぶんしんの変化へんげか
（カカシ）なっ
I'm finished if it even grazes me...
（カカシ）かすっただけでアウトだな
（サクラ）チッ
（カカシ）忍戦術の心得 その３
Shinobi Battle Skills, part three...
Ninjutsu!
忍術にんじゅつ
The speed of his seal forming...
（サクラ）印を結ぶスピードが…
（ナルト）速すぎるってばよ
It's way too fast!
（カカシ）はあ～
火遁かとん 豪火球ごうかきゅうの術
Fire Style! Fireball Jutsu!
（ナルト）うっ…
（サクラ）うわっ
カカシ先生は…
Where's Kakashi Sensei?
あっ…
Earth Style: Headhunter Jutsu!
土遁どどん 心中斬首しんちゅうざんしゅの術
えっ？
うっ うわっ
（カカシ）影分身か
A Shadow Clone, huh?!
水遁すいとん 水龍弾すいりゅうだんの術
Water Style! Water Dragon Missile!
（ナルト）うわっ 何？
What?!
（ナルト）うっ
（サクラ）うわっ
（ナルト）火遁 土遁 水遁を
連続で使うなんて
Using Fire Style, Earth Style
and Water Style consecutively.
普通 ありえねえってばよ
Ordinarily that's totally impossible.
He isn't called the "Copy Ninja"
for nothing...
（サクラ）コピー忍者の名は
だてじゃないわね
今になってみると
そのすごさがよく分かるわ
Now I understand how amazing he is.
Yeah...
ああ
（自来也じらいや）長期戦になりそうだのォ
This is going to be
a long-drawn-out affair.
（綱手つなで）だが 夜明けまでには
まだ だいぶある
But there's still plenty of time
until dawn.
（シズネ）はい
Yes, there is.
案外 あっけなく
決着がつくかもしれんぞ
Things might just be settled...
more quickly than you'd expect...
フフッ
ああっ
Gaara...
我愛羅
It's almost time...
そろそろだな うん
The real show's about to begin.
これからが本番だな うん
フフフッ
There!
そらよ！
He uses strange explosives...
And he's able to guide them, huh?
（我愛羅）妙な爆発物を使う
それも誘導タイプか
I've pretty much got it now.
だいたい分かった うん
（サクラ）分かっていたけど
写輪眼って とんでもない代物ね
I always knew, but...
The Sharingan is really
something else, isn't it?
ああ
Yeah...
でも それ以上に
先生の印を結ぶスピード
But even more than that,
the speed of his seal formation...
速すぎて近づくのも難しい
It's so fast it's tough for us
to even get near him...
（カカシ）はあ～
火遁 豪火球の術
Fire Style! Fireball Jutsu!
水遁 水龍弾の術
Water Style! Water Dragon Jutsu!
For the time being,
とりあえず
あの両手をどうにかしないと
we won't have a prayer of getting
the bells
鈴どころじゃないわね
unless we can do something
about both his hands.
Yeah. That Kakashi Sensei's
incredibly strong for sure.
ああ 全く
カカシ先生ってば やっぱ
むちゃくちゃ強えってばよ
He's smarter than Shikamaru.
シカマル以上の頭
He has a better sense of smell
than Kiba.
キバ以上の嗅覚
サスケ以上の写輪眼しゃりんがん
His Sharingan is better
than Sasuke's.
ゲジマユ以上の体術たいじゅつ
His Taijutsu is better than
Bushy Brow's.
And he's got way more...
experience than us...
経験も 俺たちよか
ず～っと豊富だし
（サクラ）でも カカシ先生にだって
弱点はあるはずよ
But even Kakashi Sensei must
have a weakness!
If we think hard about it...
よ～く考えれば
Hmm. A weakness, huh...?
（ナルト）はあ～ 弱点か
Oh! He does...
have a weakness?!
あ～ あった
弱点…
What?!
えっ？
（カカシ）ここまで写輪眼を
使わされるとはね
I never thought they'd make me
use my Sharingan this much...
But, oh well...
でも まあ
日の出まではもつか
I should be able to hang on
until sunrise...
手裏剣しゅりけん クナイ まだあるな
I've still got...Shuriken...
and Kunai Knives.
Whoops! Mustn't do that.
お～っと いかんいかん
This isn't like the old days.
昔と違って
They're too good for me to be
able to fight them while reading.
本を読みながら戦えるほど
楽な相手じゃない
But I want to know what happens.
けど 気になるなあ
It seems the main character
in "Make-Out Tactics"
イチャイチャタクティクスの主人公は
has some sort of incredible secret...
何か とんでもない秘密が
ありそうなんだ
I can't wait to read what's next...
早く続きが読みたい
R-Really?
（サクラ）ほんとに ほんとに
カカシ先生の弱点が分かったの？
Did you really figure out
Kakashi Sensei's weakness?
（ナルト）グフッ グフフフ…
サクラちゃん
You should be able to figure it out
カカシ先生の今までを
思い返せば分かるってばよ
if you look back on
his actions up until now.
もったいつけなくていいから
Quit stalling already...
What's his weakness, Naruto?
弱点って何よ ナルト
（ナルト）グフフフ…
それってばね
Well, you see...
（サクラ）うん うん
I get it!
（サクラ）なるほど
まさか そんな弱点があるなんて
I never thought he'd have
a weakness like that.
なっ 今までの行動を
思い返せば分かるだろ？
See?! It's clear if you think back
on his actions up until now, right?
うん うん それなら
両手を塞げるうえに
Right, right.
In addition to occupying
both his hands,
うまくいけば写輪眼も防げるかも
we might be able to seal off
his Sharingan if things go well.
そして その隙を突けば！
And then if we seize the opportunity...
ナルト やっぱあんた
意外性ナンバーワン忍者ね
Naruto...
Sure enough, you're the number one
most unpredictable Ninja!
ニヒッ
（カカシ）しかし
ヤツらの成長がうれしすぎて
Still, I was so pleased with
how much they've grown
つい はしゃぎすぎたな
that I e
今度は しばらく
ヤツらがどう出るか様子を見るか
そうと決まれば 先手必勝
こっちから仕掛けるってばよ
そうね いきましょう
よ～し
今度のは速いぜ うん
（我愛羅）ふんっ！
喝かつ！
（爆発音）
（カンタロウ）我愛羅！
（カカシ）来たな
なめられたもんだ
まっすぐ正面から
突っ込んでくるなんて
今よ ナルト！
いくぞ カカシ先生！
（カカシ）えっ
イチャイチャタクティクスの
最後のオチは
（カカシ）うっ
な… なに～！
実は 主人公が…
（カカシ）ネタバラシ
うわっ 危ない！
（カカシ）うう…
（カカシ）しまった
写輪眼のせいで
口の動きだけで言葉が分かっちまう！
（カカシ）はっ…
（カカシ）ええっ…
（ナルト）ヘヘッ
（サクラ）フフッ
（カカシ）あ～！
ハハッ 忍者は
裏の裏を読むべしって
ねっ 先生
（カカシ）フッ…
（カカシ）やられたぜ
（デイダラ）まるで 中身を守る卵の殻だな
しかし あれをガードしきるとは
すごいな うん
（我愛羅）砂瀑牢さばくろう
♪～
～♪
オチをバラすと見せかけて
カカシをはめるとは
なかなかの作戦じゃないか
まあな
でも 自来也様の本って
確か成人向けですよねえ
お前 いつ成人したんだ？
いや こんなの読んだうちに
入らねえって
つまんなかったし
10ページくらいで すぐやめたし
10ページ読んだそうです
よ～し 有罪！
ええっ？
ナルト 条令違反により
お前には ３日間
アカデミーの便所掃除を言い渡す
そんな～
次回「風影として」
（カカシ）やあ 諸君
今回は 我愛羅について解説するぞ
砂を変幻自在に操ることから
付いたあだ名は砂漠の我愛羅
砂の３兄弟の末っ子だ
体内に 砂の化身
守鶴しゅかくを宿し
その力を恐れた実の父親から
命を奪われかけるという
悲しい経験を持つ
以来 自分のためだけに戦う
修羅と化した
そんな我愛羅を
孤独から救ったのは
ナルトだった
仲間のために戦うナルトの姿を見て
我愛羅は 本当の強さとは何か
愛情とは何かを知る
木ノ葉崩し以降は
同盟国として木ノ葉の危機に加勢
現在は 砂隠れの里を統率する
風影に就任
じゃあ ここで問題だ
我愛羅の額に
書かれている文字は
いったい
なんだったか
分かるかな？
答は 愛
さて 帰って
イチャイチャ
タクティクスでも
読むかな